-嗨 -嗨，班
- Hi. - Hi! Hi, Ben.
-嗨 -厕所紧急事件
- Hi. - We have a bathroom emergency.
请用
Go ahead.
去之前，没有乔伊特别的“罗曼史”杂志在里面吧?
Before we do, are any of Joey's special "romance" magazines in there?
-没有 -可以了
- No. - Okay, all clear.
谢谢，菲比
Thanks, Phoebe.
瑞秋
That's Rachel.
随便啦
But whatever.
-那里没事吧? -现在不要跟我说话
- Everything okay in there? - Don't talk to me now.
就像他爸爸
Just like his daddy.
可以帮我一个大忙吗?
Could you do me a big favor?
院长办公室召开会议
I have a meeting at the dears office.
你能帮我照看班一小时吗?
Can you watch Ben for an hour?
-莫妮卡呢? -她不在家
- What about Monica? - She isn't home.
只有我一个人?
So it would just be me alone?
班也会在
Ben would be there.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
以前从来不曾只有我和他单独在一起
I've never done that before. Me and him, alone.
他不是前科犯
He's not an ex-con.
好，好…
Okay, okay...
-我要和他做什么? -我不知道，和他讲话
- What do I do with him? - I don't know, talk to him.
跟他娱乐，让他活着
Entertain him. Keep him alive.
-好 -班，来
- Okay. - Ben, come here.
我要把你留在这儿和瑞秋阿姨一起1小时，好吗？
I'm gonna leave you here with Aunt Rachel for about an hour, okay?
你可以吗?
Gonna be okay?
-我想可以 -我不是和你说话
- I think so. - I wasn't talking to you.
-我没事的 -好的，再见，伙计
- I'll be okay. - Okay. I'll see you soon, buddy.
-1个小时后回来 -再见，爸爸
- Be back in an hour. - Bye Dad.
-这很有趣吗? -不太有趣
- So this is fun, huh? - Not really.
-要喝东西吗? -好的
- Okay. Want something to drink? - Okay.
要喝健怡可乐吗?
Great. All right, how do you feel about Diet Coke?
-我不能喝苏打汽水 -好的
- I'm not allowed to have soda. - Okay.
我们有很多种
Well, that's pretty much all that we have.
你喝过纯玛格丽塔酒吗?（有“处女”的意思）
Have you ever had a virgin margarita?
什么是处女?
What's a virgin?
那就喝水吧
Water it is.
Friends S07E10 伦敦的真相
The One With The Truth About London
第二位牧师如何? 我还蛮喜欢他的
What about the second minister? I kind of liked him.
-你指喷口水那个? -别这样，他没那么糟
- You mean the spitter? - Come on. He wasn't that bad.
你说起来容易，你有面纱
Easy for you to say, you'd be wearing a veil.
-第三个呢? -他一直瞪着你的胸部看
- And the third guy? - He kept staring at your chest.
你能怪他吗?
Can you blame him?
我不希望我说“我愿意”时…
I don't like the idea of me saying, "I do"...
他想着“我也愿意”
...while he's thinking, "I'd do it too."
-那么我们这个问题还是没解决 -什么?
- Well, then we still have a problem. - With what?
我们需要证婚人 但他们都太无趣或是讨厌
We need someone to perform our wedding but they're all boring or annoying...
或是一直瞪着女生看
...or keep staring at the ladies.
应该让我们其中一人来证婚
You should have one of us do it.
我们是要“结婚”结婚 不是“六年级”的结婚
We're getting "married" married, not "6th-grade" married.
是真的
No, it's a real thing.
任何人都能在网络上被任命为牧师然后证婚
Anyone can be ordained on the Internet and perform weddings and stuff.
-你说真的? -我一个朋友就那样做了，完全合法
- Are you serious? - A friend of mine did it. It's totally legal.
我要!
I call it!
什么? 是我的主意!
What? It was my idea!
非常感谢你，但你们谁也不会替我们证婚
Thank you very much, but neither of you is marrying us.
提出请求，不再有任何意义了吗?
Does calling it not mean anything anymore?
我们要一位真正的牧师
We're having a legitimate clergy member.
我说正式，我指的是同性恋…
And when I say legitimate, I mean gay...
而且能控制口水的
...and in control of his saliva.
-那是柠檬罂粟籽吗? -不要吃，不新鲜了
- Is that lemon poppy seed? - You don't want these. They're stale.
-我拿到外面给鸽子吃 -我要!
- I'm leaving them outside for the pigeons. - I call them!
班，你知道，当你还是个婴儿时…
Ben, you know, when you were a baby...
我们常在一起
...we'd hang out all the time.
那时我是你爸的女朋友
I was your daddy's girlfriend.
可是你现在不是了
But you're not anymore.
-对，我不是 -因为你们当时分手了…
- No, I'm not. - Because you guys were on a break...
嘿，我们不是…
Hey, we were not on a...
不说了．班，你知道吗?
That's fine. You know what Ben?
等你长大了，我会全部告诉你…
One day when you are a lot older, I'm gonna tell you that entire story...
…边讲边喝玛格丽塔酒，好吗?
...over a real pitcher of margaritas. Okay?
-我爸什么时候会回来? -52分钟后
- Whers my daddy coming back? - 52 minutes.
你没有兄弟姐妹，嗯?
So no brothers or sisters, huh?
真好，不用分东西
That must be nice. You don't have to share stuff.
分享是好事
Sharing is good.
你就是分享的
You're one of those.
我有两个姐妹，我们彼此折磨
You know what, I had two sisters and we just tortured each other.
-真的? 像怎样? -我们会…
- Really? Like how? - Well, you know, we would...
重复另一个人说的每一句话…
...we'd repeat everything the other said...
或是从衣柜跳出去吓人…
...or we'd jump out of closets to scare each other...
或是把糖换成盐 让别人把盐洒到早餐麦片里
...or switch the sugar with salt so they put salt on their cereal.
这个不错
That's a good one.
-你喜欢吗? -是，你很好玩
- Yeah, you like that one? - Yeah, you're funny.
我很好玩?
I'm funny?
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
嘿，我有一大堆这种故事
Well, hey, I got a ton of these.
想听好故事吗? 这里就有一个好故事
You want a good one? Here's a good one.
拿一个25分铜板…
You take a quarter...
把边缘涂黑
...and you blacken the edge, right?
然后说：我打赌，你不能用这枚铜板…
And then you say, "I bet you can't roll this quarter...
滚过你的下巴而不离开你的脸
...to your chin without it leaving your face."
等他们这么做了，会在脸正中央留下一条线
And when they do it, they're left with a line down the center of their face.
我可以对你这样吗?
Can I do it to you?
班，我是幽默，但我不笨
I'm funny, Ben, but I'm not stupid.
你们找到证婚人了吗?
So did you find anyone to marry you yet?
没有，但那位“对莫妮卡冲动”的牧师打电话来…
No, but "Horny for Monica" minister called...
想知道我们是否还在一起
...wondering if we're still together.
-我们永远找不到人了 -那么让我来
- We'll never find anybody. - Then let me do it.
-乔伊…--我想过了
- Joey... - I've been thinking.
我是个演员，我在人前不会紧张
I'm an actor, so I won't get nervous in front of people.
-乔伊，请... -不，不，不
- Joey, please... - No, no, no.
我不会喷口水，也不会瞪着莫妮卡的胸部看
I won't spit and I won't stare at Monica's breasts.
大家都知道我喜欢的是臀部
Everyone knows I'm an ass man.
-那倒是真的 -最重要的是…
- That's true. - The most important thing...
不是一位几乎不认识你的陌生人替你证婚
...is, it won't be some stranger who barely knows you.
而会是我，我发誓，我会做得很好
It'll be me. And I swear, I'll do a really good job.
还有，我爱你们，这对我意义重大
Plus, I love you guys and it would really mean a lot to me.
-我们还没找到其他人 -也许有点酷
- Well, we haven't found anybody else. - Might be kind of cool.
-我可以吗? -好，你可以
- So I can do it? - Yeah, you can do it.
好! 好!
All right! Okay!
好，我要开始准备我的演说
Okay, I gotta get started on my speech.
等一下
Wait a minute.
网络上任命的牧师，还是可以做爱，对吧?
Internet ministers can have sex, right?
-嘿，菲比，怎么样? -头痛，非常痛
- Hey, Pheebs. How's it going? - I have a headache. A horrible headache.
-很遗憾．要我给你拿点什么吗？-天哪，你别唠叨了
- I'm sorry. Can I get you something? - Oh, my God, you've got to stop chattering.
来吃几片吧
Here, take a couple of these.
-什么? -止痛药
- What is it? - It's Hexedrin.
不，我不相信西方医学
Oh, no, I don't believe in Western medicine.
如果一直按住这个穴位
If you just apply pressure to these points right here...
你的手开始疼，而头还会疼，谢谢
Then your hands starts to hurt and you still have a headache, so thanks.
在药效起作用前，你坐到沙发上吧
While we're waiting for these pills to kick in, I'm gonna sit you down on the couch.
来吧．头下放些柔软的垫子
Come on. Get some nice soft pillows under your head.
我会打开电视，随便你看什么
I'm gonna turn the TV on. You can watch whatever you want.
坐下，我给你泡茶，然后给你按摩脚
Sit down. I'm gonna make you some tea, and then I'm gonna rub your feet.
我的头!
My head!
来了
Coming.
我要找你麻烦
I have a bone to pick with you.
-噢！ -对
- Uh-oh. - Yes.
班学了一个恶作剧
Ben learned a little trick.
-他是不是…? -对，是的
- Oh, did he pull the old...? - That's right. That's right.
马桶座上包了保鲜膜…
Saran wrap on the toilet seat...
于是尿尿时喷得到处都是
...so the pee goes everywhere.
-哦，那个啊 -对，那个
- Oh, that. - Yeah, that.
你知道我最恨恶作剧的
You know I hate practical jokes.
恶作剧很恶劣，很笨，我不要我儿子学会这些
They're mean, they're stupid and I don't want my son learning them.
马桶包了保鲜膜? 那没有一点点好笑吗?
Saran wrap on the toilet seat? Isn't that just a little funny?
-我赤脚 -哦
- I was barefoot. - Oh.
我说的就是这个
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
你不是笑别人，正是笑他们
You're not laughing with someone, you're laughing at them.
取笑别人是不好的
And laughing at someone is not nice.
你也是他们中的一个
So you're one of those too.
你只有教他马桶这一件，对不对?
Tell me, the toilet thing is the only thing you taught him, right?
对
Yes.
太神奇了，我的头完全不痛了
It' amazing. My headache is completely gone.
-那些是什么药? -止痛药
- What were those pills called? - Hexedrin.
我爱你，止痛药
I love you Hexedrin.
噢，还有故事呢
Oh, look, it comes with a story.
菲比．上面写的是副作用
Phoebe, those are like the side effects and stuff.
什么?
Say what?
可能有的副作用
You know, the possible side effects.
噢，我的天哪
Oh, my God.
头晕，紧张，嗜睡
"Dizziness. Nervousness. Drowsiness.
脸部肿胀，恶心，头痛...
Facial swelling. Nausea. Headache..."
头痛
Headache.
“呕吐．胃出血，肝损害”
"Vomiting. Stomach bleeding. Liver damage."
要不是吃了你这些该死的药片我都忘了这些症状
I don't recall any of these coming up when you gave me these little death capsules.
哦，对不起．“超力”死亡药片
Oh, I'm sorry. "Extra strength" death capsules.
那些不会发生的．只是因为法律原因写上去
None of that ever happens. They just put it on there for legal reasons.
为什么?
Why?
预防它会发生
In case it happens.
-嘿 -向乔伊崔比亚尼牧师打招呼
- Hey. - Say hello to Reverend Joey Tribbiani.
-你被任命了?-对
- You got ordained? - Yeah.
刚上完网，网上好多色情图片
Just got off the Internet. Man, there's a lot of porn out there.
我们的牧师
Our minister.
现在我可以正式为任何人证婚了
I can now officially marry anybody I want.
你们很开心嘛，要是结婚的话 记得给我电话
Hey, you guys seem happy. If you ever want to get marry, you give me a call.
不结婚的话，也请给我电话
If not, you give me a call.
我有肝损害
I have liver damage.
菲比，你的肝在这里
Phoebe, your liver is right here.
那我一定是器官移位了
Okay, well, then I must be disoriented.
我已经写下我在婚礼要说的话，要听吗?
I started on what I'm gonna say for the ceremony. Want to hear it?
注意，这只是第一篇草稿，所以…
Listen, this is just the first draft, so...
今天我们齐聚此处，在这个喜悦的场合．
"We are gathered here today on this joyous occasion...
来庆祝莫妮卡和钱德之间特别的爱
...to celebrate the special love that Monica and Chandler share.
这是奠基在付出和接受．
It is a love based on giving and receiving...
拥有和分享的爱
...as well as having and sharing.
他们付出和拥有的爱被分享和接受了
And the love that they give and have is shared and received.
借着这样的拥有和付出…
And through this having and giving...
以及分享接受…
...and sharing and receiving...
我们同样分享，爱，和拥有…
...we too can share and love and have...
还有接受
...and receive."
要不要打电话给喷口水的?
Should we call the spitter?
-嘿，瑞秋 -嘿
- Hey, Rachel. - Hi.
好惊喜，你怎么来这里?
What a surprise. What are you doing here?
我正好在附近…
I was just in the neighborhood...
经过你家，我想，卡萝和可爱的小班…
...and I passed by your building and thought, "What's up with Carol...
不知道怎么样?
...and sweet little Ben?"
-真好，请进 -好
- That's nice. Well, come on in. - Okay.
我来煮咖啡，然后我们可以聊天
I'll make some coffee and we can chat.
好啊，很好
I'd love that. I would love that.
可爱的小班呢?
So where is sweet little Ben?
我想和小…
I would love to have a little...
找到他了!
I found him!
好好笑，过来
Very funny. Come here.
这就是我来找你谈的原因
That is exactly why I've come here to talk to you, okay?
-瑞秋，要加糖吗? -好，但…
- Rachel, you want sugar? - Yes, but...
我的咖啡要不要加糖?
Do I want sugar in my coffee?
不要，只要加牛奶就好，谢谢
No, just some milk would be good, Carol. Thanks.
记得我昨天教你的那些东西吗?
Remember all that stuff I taught you yesterday?
“记得我昨天教你的那些东西吗?”
"Remember all that stuff I taught you yesterday?"
-不要这样-“不要这样”
- Don't do that. - "Don't do that."
-你爸爸不喜欢恶作剧-“你爸爸不喜欢恶作剧”
- Your dad doesn't like pranks.
- "Your dad doesn't like pranks."
-可恶!-“可恶”!
- Oh, damn it! - "Oh, damn it!"
不，不要这么说
No! Don't say that.
-可恶! -重覆我的说话
- Damn it! - Go back to repeating.
-可恶! -真烂!
- Damn it! - Oh, crap!
“真烂”
"Oh, crap!"
我的脸好像肿了．我的脸肿了吗?
I feel like my face is swelling. Is my face swelling?
菲比，你的脸没事．你不会有事的
Phoebe, your face is fine. None of this stuff is gonna happen to you.
-不要像个孩子般的 -有意思，你应该那样叫我
- Stop being a baby. - Interesting you should call me that...
以防我没有这些症状
...now that I may never have one.
好，我又写了一些，准备好了吗?
Okay, I got some more written, ready?
是，好
Yeah, okay.
当我想到这两位付出者和接受者所分享的爱…
"When I think of the love that these two givers and receivers share...
我禁不住嫉妒之后一生的拥有和爱…
...I can't help but envy the lifetime ahead of having and loving...
和付出…我想不出这儿要用什么字
...and giving..." And then I can't think of a good word for right here.
-用“接受”如何? -对
- How about "receiving"? - Yes!
乔伊，这不是不好…
See, Joe, not that that's not great...
但朋友证婚的好处就是…
...but one cool thing about having a friend perform the ceremony...
能够和我们有关
...is that it can be about us.
可以你个人的角度，你可以说说我们的小故事
It can be more personal. You can tell stories about us.
就像你和我去亚特兰大城时…
Like the time you and I went to Atlantic City...
…我让你笑个不停，你把整个牛排吐了出来
...and I made you laugh so hard you threw up your whole steak?
不
No.
不是我们的事
Not us.
是我们的事
Us.
明白了，对不起
I got you. Sorry.
你曾让他吐过吗?
So did you ever make him throw up a whole anything?
你给他吃过毒药片，眼睛出血吗?
Did you ever feed him a poison capsule that made him bleed from the eyes?
不是那样的
It doesn't say that.
突然有人明白了所有副作用
Suddenly somebody knows all about the side effects.
乔伊，我们要你讲故事 不过是浪漫故事，好听的故事
Joey, we want you to tell stories, but romantic stories, nice stories.
好! 我可以谈伦敦 当你们搞在一起
Okay! Maybe I'll talk about London, when you hooked up.
我不会说“搞在一起”…
Only I won't say "hooked up"...
我会说：他们美丽的旅程…
...l'll say, "began their beautiful journey...
-对了 -由“做了”开始
- There you go. ...by doing it."
-乔伊 -好吧
- Joe. - Okay, all right.
所以是怎么开始的? 你们的双眼越过房间相遇
So how did it happen? Did your eyes meet across the room...
然后你在浴缸里，她在喂你吃草莓?
...then you're in the bathtub and she's feeding you strawberries?
-那不是发生在你和伴娘身上吗? -对
- Isn't that what happened to you? - Yeah!
我叫它“伦敦风格”
I call that "London style."
没发生在我们身上
That didn't happen with us.
也许你应该说有，因为“伦敦风格”听起来不错
Maybe you should say it is, because "London style" sounds nice.
好，嗯…
Okay, uh...
那天晚上我很难过 因为有个家伙以为我是罗斯的妈
I was sad that night because this guy thought I was Ross' mom.
钱德对我很好，一直安慰我…
And Chandler was really sweet and he consoled me and...
-而我们喝了很多 -好啊，宝贝
...we drank too much. - Yeah, baby.
我很绅士地陪她走回旅馆房间，道了晚安
I was a gentleman and I walked her to her hotel room and said good night.
-但那晚的晚些时候…-好啊，宝贝
- But then, later that night... - Yeah, baby.
可爱的睡衣，真的想在伦敦过得多采多姿?
Cute P.J.s. Really living it up here in London, huh?
我想不会再有人来，现在已经…
Well, I wasn't exactly expecting company after...
9点15分
...9:15.
乔伊在吗?
Is Joey here?
上次我看到他时 他和伴娘和一篮草莓在一起
Last I saw he was with a bridesmaid and a bucket of strawberries.
你不会还在为那个家伙的话生气吧?
You're not still upset about what that guy told you, are you?
你不会吗?
wouldn't you be?
这是一个很感人的时刻，你又喝了很多…
It's been a really emotional time and you've had a lot to drink...
你必须要让这件事过去，好吗?
You have to let that go, okay?
你是今晚屋里最美的女人
You were the most beautiful woman in the room tonight.
真的?
Really?
你说笑? 你是大部份屋里最美的女人…
You kidding? You're the most beautiful woman in most rooms...
噢，发生什么事了?
Whoa, what's going on?
我们亲嘴了
We just made out.
-我们亲嘴了? -现在没有
- We're making out? - Not anymore.
-可是我们不这样的 -我知道，我以为会很好玩
- But we don't do that. - I know, I thought it would be fun.
你有多醉?
How drunk are you?
醉到知道我想这么做 但没到你觉得内疚的地步
Enough to know I want to do this. Not so much that you should feel guilty.
这是最好的程度
That's the perfect amount.
-你知道哪里奇怪吗? -哪里?
- You know what's weird? - What?
-感觉一点都不奇怪 -我知道
- This doesn't feel weird. - I know.
-你的吻功很棒，-我吻了超过4个女人
- You're a really good kisser. - Well, I have kissed over four women.
-钻到被窝里? -好
Want to get under the covers? Okay.
哇，你好快!
Wow, you are really fast!
我想你会欣赏速度
It bodes well for me that speed impresses you.
-我们要裸体相见了 -对
- We're gonna see each other naked. - Yep.
-同时? -数到三?
- At the same time? - Count of three?
一，二，三
One, two, three.
我想我们的友谊很有效得被毁了
Well, I think it's safe to say our friendship is effectively ruined.
反正我们本来关系也没那么好
Eh, we weren't that close anyway.
乔伊，乔伊，乔伊…!
Joey, Joey, Joey...!
嘿
Hey.
嘿，乔伊，我在看电影…
Hey, Joe. I was just watching a movie...
老兄，对不起
Oh, dude, I'm so sorry.
不是!
No!
没事，我还跟伴娘在一起
It's cool, I'm still with my bridesmaid.
保险套在哪儿?
Where are the condoms?
在那边，我的袋子里
In my bag over there.
可以留一个给我吗?
Could you leave me one?
给你自己?
For just you?
对
Yeah.
为什么不跟我下楼呢 下面很多正点的女孩
Why don't you come downstairs with me. There's some really nice girls down there.
不，我没事
No, I'm fine.
好，给你，老兄
All right. There you go, buddy.
你去疯吧
Go nuts.
原来是为了那件事用的?
That's what that was?
因为那另外一件事 我想你猜到了什么，不过对我无所谓
Because that other thing, I thought you were onto something.But it did nothing for me.
可以换个话题吗? 因为我也无所谓
Can we change the topic? Because it's really doing nothing for me.
如果我没留一个给你 你们两个可能永远不会在一起
If I hadrt left you one, you two might've never gotten together.
想像一下，如果我照原来计划送了一个妓女上去会怎么样?
Imagine if I had sent that hooker like I was gonna?
就像在星星上一样
It's like it was in the stars.
是啊，你们是注定在一起的
Yeah, totally meant to be.
告诉他你原先那晚是要去找谁的
Tell him who you originally wanted to hook up with that night.
-什么? -什么?
- What? - What?
什么?
What?
你原先是要去找找谁的?
Who did you originally want to hook up with?
好吧，不要生气
Okay, fine, but please don't be upset.
我那时真的很沮丧好吗? 而且醉得很厉害
I was really depressed, okay? And really drunk.
我想做又笨又无意义的事，我只想上床
I wanted something stupid and meaningless. I just wanted sex.
所以那晚我到你们房间…
So, when I went to your room that night...
其实是要找乔伊的
...I was actually looking for Joey.
好啊，宝贝
Yeah, baby.
不，宝贝
No, baby.
哦，我的天
Oh, my God.
你来找乔伊的?
You came looking for Joey?
-你有计划要告诉我吗? -没有，我觉得这不重要
- Were you planning on telling me this? - No, I didn't think it was important.
这不重要? 这不重要?
It's not important? It's not important?
如果没有那个伴娘 你嫁的会是他而不是我
If it wasn't for a bridesmaid, you'd be marrying him not me.
不，问题是，是你那晚在那里
No. The point is, it was you that was there that night.
我要嫁的是你．我爱的是你
It is you that I'm marrying. It is you that I fell in love with.
这种爱是建立在拥有，付出，得到
And it is a love that is based on having and giving and receiv...
奇怪，我一生最浪漫的夜晚 可我却是第二名
Weird. The most romantic night of my life and I'm runner-up.
你知道我有多高兴乔伊不在那儿吗?
Do you know how unbelievably glad I am that Joey wasn't there?
嘿!
Hey!
虽然我是神职人员 可是我还是有感觉的
I'm a man of the cloth, but I still have feelings.
现在你不可能替我们证婚
There's no way you're doing this wedding now, okay?
什么? 不公平，不是我的错
What? That's not fair. It's not my fault.
我和伴娘在一起
I was with my bridesmaid.
而且谁说我会答应的?
And who's to say I would've said yes?
我是说，我会答应的
I mean, I would've said yes.
你把这件事看得太严重了
You are making way too big a deal out of this.
最后都很好啊
Everything worked out okay.
只是很奇怪，好吗?
It's just weird, okay?
我不要在我立下婚誓时心里有着你和莫妮卡的影像
I don't want to be saying my vows with the mental image of you and Monica.
我需要…我不知道我要什么，我要去散步
I need... I don't know what I need. I need a walk.
-等一下，钱德 没有什么大不了的 -对我是
- Wait, Chandler, it's not a big deal. - It is to me.
你想和蝙蝠侠上床，结果以罗宾打发了
You wanted to sleep with Batman and settled for Robin.
-这太扯了 -不，罗宾是同性恋
- This is crazy. - No, Robin is so gay.
菲比，你在想什么啊? 你怎么能告诉他呢?
Phoebe, what were you thinking? How could you tell him that?
我不知道，对不起，脱口而出的
I don't know. I'm sorry, it just came out.
这是副作用
It's a side effect.
-我们都同意了? -不再恶作剧
- So now what have we agreed? - No more pranks.
-还有呢? -你和爸爸不是在分手
- What else? - You and Daddy were not on a break.
很好
Very good.
瑞秋，你在这里干什么?
Rachel, what are you doing here?
拜访我的好朋友卡萝
I'm just visiting my good friend Carol.
-你的好朋友? -对
- Your good friend? - Yeah.
她姓什么?
What's her last name?
卡萝…
Carol...
-同性恋-很好
...Lesbian. - Nice.
-还有，我脸上那条线… -什么线?
- By the way, that line down my face...- What line?
在今天最后一堂课…
"What Line?" The line that prompted a student...
让一个学生说：
...in my last class of the day to say:
“老兄，你从来不洗脸吗?”的那条线
"Dude, don't you ever wash your face?"
好，我很抱歉，对不起没有告诉你
All right I'm sorry. I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
-但当时你已经疯了，-当然我会发疯了
- But you were so mad already. - Of course I was mad.
我跟你说过我讨厌那东西 知道吗? 并不有趣
I told you I hate this stuff. Okay? It's not funny.
-嘿，罗斯 -嗨
- Hey, Ross. - Hi.
-什么并不有趣? -恶作剧
- What's not funny? - Practical jokes.
我认为很有趣
Well, I think they're funny.
-你的脸上有条线 -什么?
- You have a line down your face. - What?
-好吧，也许你不觉得好笑 -噢，我的天哪
- Okay, maybe they're not funny to you... - Oh, my God!
还有卡萝
Or Carol.
但是孩子们觉得有趣．这伤害到谁呢?
But they're funny to kids. And who is it hurting?
告诉你伤害到谁吧 伤害了在体操课被偷光衣服的孩子
I'll tell you who it hurts. It hurts the kid who has all his clothes stolen in gym class...
以致他到校长办公室时 身上只戴着手套
...so he has to go to the principal's office wearing nothing but a catcher's mitt.
那是你?
That was you?
我们听说过你中学的趣事
We heard about you in junior high.
你是否真的挥舞着拳头喊“我会报复的!”
Did you really just shake your fist in the air and shout, "I will be revenged!"
我会的!
I will be!
我不要你再教我儿子那些东西
I don't want you teaching my son that stuff anymore.
-好吗? -好，好
- Okay? - Fine. Fine.
我一教他那些东西 他叫我“好玩的瑞秋阿姨”
Once I taught him that stuff, he called me "fun Aunt Rachel."
我喜欢做好玩的瑞秋阿姨
And I loved being fun Aunt Rachel.
我要做回无聊，不舒服的瑞秋阿姨
But I'll go back to being boring and uncomfortable Aunt Rachel.
不，我不是那个意思
No, it's not what I want.
很高兴你们能建立感情，但…
I'm glad you guys were bonding but...
他没有任何兄弟姐妹
Look, he doesn't have any siblings.
有人得教他这些东西
Somebody has to teach him this stuff.
我没有教他任何正常6岁小孩不知道的事
I haven't taught him anything a normal 6-year-old doesn't know.
-好烂! -我要走了
- Crap! - I gotta go.
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你要这个酥饼吗? 是给我的，但它比较想和你睡
You want this scone? It came for me but it would rather sleep with you.
什么都没发生
Nothing even happened.
-我知道你要在婚礼上 -不，如果你不希望我
- Look, I know you want to do the wedding... - No. If you don't want me to do it...
我接受．我不在乎．我只是不想你生气
...I accept that. I don't care about that. I just don't want you to be upset.
我怎么能不生气?
How can I not be upset?
我终于和这个很棒的女人坠入爱河…
I finally fall in love with this fantastic woman...
而她最初要的是你
...and it turns out she wanted you first.
是啊，某一个晚上的半小时
Yeah, for like a half an hour one night.
钱德，她要和你共度一生
Chandler, she wants you for the rest of her life.
你真幸运
You're so lucky.
如果我不在场，我将会失去什么
Look what I missed out on by not being there.
你知道吗?
Although, you know what?
永远不会像你们这样
It could never have worked out like you guys did.
因为你们天生一对
Because you guys are perfect for each other.
我们看着你们，看到你们在一起，就是…
We look at you and we see you together, and it just...
很配，你知道吗?
...it fits, you know?
你就是知道能持续终生
And you just know it's gonna last forever.
这就是你该讲的
That's what you should say.
什么?
What?
当你替我们证婚时，那就是你该说的
When you're marrying us, that's what you should say.
真的? 我可以替你们证婚吗?
Really? I could do it?
我希望你替我证婚
I'd love you to do it.
嘿
Hey.
不过那些将是你的演讲，必须一模一样的
But those are the words. Those exact words.
我不太记得了…
Well, I don't remember exactly but...
是关于拥有和付出和分享和接受
...it's pretty much about having and giving and sharing and receiving.
抱歉要再麻烦你一次…
I'm sorry to do this to you again...
你可以替我照顾一下班吗?
...but could you look after Ben for a little bit?
我在学校有个会要开
I've got this meeting at school.
他说要找“好玩的”瑞秋阿姨
And he asked for his "fun" Aunt Rachel.
当然，我们会很开心的，是不是，班?
Well, of course I will watch him. We have fun, don't we, Ben?
-好，待会见 -好 （粪便）
- Okay, see you later, pal. - Okay.
-等一下，班，我不能这么做 -什么?
- Wait a minute. Ben, I can't do it. - What?
不能让他这样走掉，他还要开会
Can't let him go out that way. He's got a meeting.
-你背后有东西 -什么?
- You got something here on your back.- What?
好，好极了
That's great. That is great.
班，我们才说完什么?
What did we just finish talking about, Ben?
“班，我们才说完什么?”
"What did we just finish talking about, Ben?"
好，够了，过来，年轻人，你麻烦大了!
All right, that's it. Come here. You are in big trouble young man!
班，过来，我不是开玩笑的!
Ben, come here! I am not kidding!
你要停止…
You gotta stop doing...
我的天啊!
My God!
-你们两个没事了? -是啊
- So you guys doing okay? - Yeah.
我们谈过了，莫妮卡让我知道我反应过度了
We talked and Monica made me see that I overreacted a little bit.
-有些事是比较重要的 -是啊，宝贝
- Some things are more important.- Yeah, baby.
很高兴你们没事了，但我一直在想…
I'm really glad you guys are okay, but I just keep thinking...
如果你们两个在一起会是什么样子
...what would've happened if you two had hooked up.
亲爱的，晚饭好了!
Honey, dinner's ready!
我的小厨师今晚替我做了什么?
What's my little chef got for me tonight?
你最喜欢的
Your favorite.
起司炒鸡
Fried stuff with cheese.
很多很多!
And lots of it!
谢谢，甜心
Thanks, sweetheart.
来亲一个
Give me a little sugar...
来，来，来
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
你好吗?
How you doing?
来了
Here you go.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
这是六小时见效的药
This is a six-hour pill.
到时间了! 我走出树林了
That's it! I'm out of the woods.
太好了
What a relief.
很好嘛
Good for you.
心头大石终于落地了
It's like a huge weight has been lifted.
因为，你看，没有脱发，没有皮疹，没有麻疹
Because, look, no hair loss, no rash, no hives.
我太高兴了!
I'm just so happy!
因为，不会气喘，没有短时兴奋症
Because, no shortness of breath, no temporary euphoria...